<resources>
    <!-- Media Directories -->
    <string name="media_directories">Media Directories for Shared Playlist</string>
    <string name="media_directories_brief">Syncplay will search any media directories you specify here in order to find a name that a shared playlist is playing. It is much better if you specify small directories as the searching operation can throttle and be very slow.</string>
    <string name="media_directories_save">Save &amp; Exit</string>
    <string name="media_directories_clear_all">Clear all</string>
    <string name="media_directories_clear_all_confirm">Are you sure you want to clear the list ?</string>
    <string name="media_directories_add_folder">Add folder</string>
    <string name="media_directories_delete">Remove from list</string>
    <string name="media_directories_show_full_path">Show full path</string>
    <string name="media_directories_going_for_pick_rationale">"Select directory to save playlist to as a file"</string>


    <string name="about_version">• Version: %s</string>
    <string name="about_developed_by">• Developed by: yuroyami</string>
    <string name="about_client_is_unofficial_disclaimer">• This client is not official. Thanks to official Syncplay team for their amazing software.</string>
    <string name="about_client_platforms">• Syncplay is officially available for Windows, macOS, and Linux.</string>
    <string name="about_official_website">• Official Website: www.syncplay.pl</string>

    <string name="tips_dontshowmetips">Don't show me tips</string>
    <string name="tips_did_ya_know">Did ya know?</string>

    <string-array name="tips">
        <item>For shared playlists to work, Syncplay needs to know where your media files are stored. Add your media folders in 'Settings > General > Media Directories for Shared Playlist'.</item>
        <item>Want to use the video player solo? Select a player, tap the Syncplay logo above, then choose 'Offline Mode'.</item>
        <item>You can always reset settings to their default states by going to 'Settings -> Advanced -> Reset to Default'</item>
        <item>Joining the same room repeatedly? Save it as a shortcut on your device for one-tap access by clicking the small button next to 'Join Room'.</item>
        <item>Each player has different strengths. If one doesn't work well with your video format, try another.</item>
        <item>Syncplay Mobile allows you to play media from direct links. However, YouTube is NOT supported, yet.</item>
        <item>If you want to minimize the room temporarily without leaving, you can go into "Picture-in-Picture" mode where the screen is a small floating screen above other apps.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>